How
Are we going?
So we just pulled into Santa Barbara, California maybe for the start of the Northern California road
Trip.
So LA to San Francisco along the Pacific One, the highway.
But parts of it are closed so we're gonna have to like work around that.
Anyway we're going to Santa Barbara to San Luis Obispo.
Pronounce that so badly, I bet.
Big Sur National Park or National Forest, whatever it is, for two days in a cabin.
And then up to like Carmel-by-the-Sea kind of area.
I haven't booked that yet, but like around there.
And then into San Francisco for a 49ers game.
But anyway, we are losing daylight.
We're going into Santa Barbara now.
So yeah, let's go.
Wow, Santa Barbara is unbelievably beautiful.
I am completely in love with it.
It's exactly what Ali predicted.
She's like, you're going to do this California road trip and you're going to ask, can we move there?
I'm already thinking about moving.
Place is beautiful and now I'm off to get some authentic tacos I'm gonna completely butcher
The pronunciation of the place but we'll find out what it's called together in like two seconds
Yeah, we're stopped.
Yeah.
Santa Barbara, absolutely 10 out of 10.
The food, the people, the weather, the architecture, the everything.
I can't tell if it's just because, you know, it's the first stop of the roadie and I'm just completely
Biased because I'm also really excited to be on this road trip.
Do wish I had more time here.
I do not have more time here.
We got to keep going.
Yeah, Santa Barbara, absolutely 10 out of 10.
So we're staying at the madonna inn which is a crazy hotel that I have been told about by Allie's
Brother, they came on a family road trip up through here and stayed one night here as just like a
Novelty because it's like so wacky.
All the rooms I think are individually styled and designed, different themed.
Mine is an Indian, like a Native American themed room.
I just went into like check-in and went through like the cafe lobby and check-in area and it is like
Hilarious.
It's so so cool like the carpet the designs the thought like it's so fun so um yeah that's
Where we're bunking tonight
We repeat the waterfall start
This place is hilarious
As a lot of you may know by now and remember it is tradition on this channel that we
Do a first look at a hotel room together and I feel like this, what we're about to
Do, this one we're about to do is going to be one of the best yet for all the wackiest
Of reasons.
Native American theme with the stone walls is what the postcard was saying and then like the brown walls
As well I love wow these are cool
Fortunately I can't do my other surprise which I was planning on doing today um it was going to be
Driving out to a a navy base that has fighter jets um because I love fighter jets and
I really wanted to see some but it's like it adds two hours plus to the trip and then I
End up missing like a lot of the coastal road which is where I am right now.
I've stopped because it's absolutely beautiful So yeah, no fighter jets, unfortunately
Because of that I'm kind of like ahead of schedule now, so I just pulled over at this beautiful place
It looks like it has a hike or it kind of jazz so Let's go check it out
Oh my god, there's a fighter jet at the view that I just said I was going to see.
No way!
I
Was saying that I'm not going to drive inland and waste like hours not along the coast driving to the
Desert to go to the base where the fighter jets are and one just flies by at the most beautiful
Spot that I just happened to randomly pull over at.
What?
Car is moving fast down the freeway to
Anywhere.
We are going somewhere new tonight.
I ain't letting you out of my sight.
This might be crazy I hope it is Maybe this is what we
Do
We leave it all
Up for sale Cause we are going somewhere
Are
You
Serious?
Look at where I've just woken up.
It's a cabin in the redwoods.
Well actually, I think it counts as redwoods.
These look like redwoods behind it.
I think it counts as Redwoods because all the hikes I've been looking up in the area
Say, like, if you go...
Anyway, I'm completely skipping the entire point here.
I've woken up in Big Sur National Park.
Oh, oh, oh.
I just drove straight yesterday from, like, that Taco Bell.
It was a long drive, like, three hours up into Big Sur, which is where we're spending the next two
Days.
And I skipped tradition, unfortunately, of showing you the room with me.
Like you know getting a first look because I got here so late but anyway we can do that right
Now and also it was dark and you wouldn't have been able to appreciate it so yeah
Sick
There's
No signs or anything for this first stop.
I found it on TikTok though, so like, it has to be legit.
I mean, it looks unbelievably beautiful.
But I mean honestly I've had to stop myself from pulling over like 10 times since leaving my accommodation to
Get to here and that was about 15 minutes ago.
Also I was talking to the guy in the gas station on the way here at like getting protein bars
Water that kind of stuff and he was like really upset a bit because he obviously owns a business here
And he was upset about the highway closure so there's a highway closure on Pacific on California 1 that disconnects
Big Sur National from like Los Angeles, so you have to like come all the way around and go
Inland, which is what I ended up doing yesterday.
And that's bad for business because it means this place is like empty, well you know, empty compared to what
It usually is, which is really upsetting for the locals and for business I'm sure.
He did say to me though, he was like, look, enjoy it like this, you're never going to get it
Like this again.
Like you go and enjoy it.
But for me and all of us businesses, it's slumping at the moment, which is really sad.
Look at this.
I can just walk along Pacific One, California Highway through Big Sur National Park and
There's no cars.
So I was just driving by and I saw this cute little sign for a public library that's open.
So it's in the redwood forest, tucked into the trees.
We've got to stop and have a look, don't we?
It's
So cool and it's a non-profit library that's effectively turned into a bookstore so I just had to grab something
I grabbed darwin um origin of the species bookshelf staple I haven't read it and it's tiny and it fits
In my suitcase because I have like absolutely no weight.
Look, this place is just unreal.
Look at their backyard.
Hi, bunny.
The road is so rough and rocky.
This is the last stop.
I'm going to go back to the hotel.
The hotel is on the left.
The water is so clear that I don't feel like going home.
The sea is so clear.
I was looking forward to the next time I would go there.
I'm going to the hotel in a hurry.
So solo traveling is super what's the word interesting I guess I mean you just got to be like aside
From the obvious which is being okay with time spent on your own and sitting at
A restaurant by yourself what I personally find the most difficult is not sharing the experiences directly with someone and
It's extremely obvious to me because it's in direct contrast to what I've just come from where um Ali and
I were in Zion National Park together for five days straight doing this every single day and don't get me
Wrong this is absolutely unbelievable but I catch myself thinking oh this is so beautiful I can't wait to bring
Someone back here or come again or do it again with a group which obviously shows that my brain is
Thinking that I would like a companion with me right about now I mean it's kind of fun because you're
With me but you know what I I mean, like a side-by-side companion.
I think that's, for me personally, the hardest part about solo traveling.
Good morning.
The reason why I'm so early, it's like 6.30, it's still dark outside, is that we're going to go and
Do one of the main hikes of Pixar.
Point Lobos Loop.
So it's like 10 kilometers, 6 miles, estimated 2.5 hours.
Thank you
For
Watching.
Oh my god.
So I have to pull over and sit down and sit in the gutter to tell you about what just
Happened.
I was sitting at that cafe where you saw where I had that unbelievable chocolate and almond croissant.
I was sitting there and I just pulled out my book and started reading it.
And it's called The Fabric of the Cosmos by Brian Green, who's a professional, a theoretical physicist.
And he's on string theory, blah, blah, blah.
There's this really chatty older couple sitting right next to me.
And then the lady just turned to me instantly.
She's like, I'm sorry to interrupt, but what book are you reading?
And I was like, oh, it's this book.
She's like, no way.
My husband is a physicist.
The husband, like, his eyes lit up when he saw me.
Came over.
He's an 81 year old guy.
He like owns his own company.
He's just like one of the more in shape and mentally with it 81 year olds I've ever come across
And he came and like pulled up the chair next to me and sat and we just sat there and
Talked physics for like An hour and a half while I was doing that his wife was sitting next to
Him and she's like Would look behind him and look at me and be like you don't know what you've
Just done He hasn't talked physics like this with anyone in years.
You've opened a can of worms for me um he's never gonna shut up about this and he would like
Sit there and like put his arm out and like tell her to stop like get her to stop talking
Because he's trying to think and then we would keep going and ask more questions about it was one of
The more wholesome and like beautiful and fun as well so fun because like we were learning physics off each
Other just sitting there at table it's one of those like amazing interactions like a beautiful interaction I'm just like
Beaming ear to ear it was so fun so the outcome of that is that I haven't seen any of
Carmel by the sea other than like three streets so I'm gonna actually go and explore now
So I realised when I walked down to the beach just before that I've been in
California for three days now and I have not
Jumped in the ocean yet.
So let's go change that.
So
Yo teleporting us around we are currently in um san francisco
Four I'm just showing you actually because I bought it today.
Boom.
San Francisco 49ers game.
Oh, yeah.
It's my first ever NFL game.
I'm so hyped for it.
Beyond hyped for it.
But I literally have to go right now.
Also, I can't bring my camera.
I've been researching.
They don't let you go in with like big camera setups.
So I'm not even going to risk it.
Oh, yeah.
Football.
Okay, I have to go.
I'm going to film everything I possibly can on my iPhone.
Who knows how it's going to turn out.
We're going to have fun.
First ever NFL game.
Woo!
While I waited for the sun to shine I was crying on my own
It was always the time all along
Yeah, I waited through the summertime For the sun to come
Around Come around, come around, come around
Oh, the rain will beat the sun Yeah, yeah, yeah Cause your heart is on the run
Yeah, yeah, yeah yo that game last night was so much fun like ridiculous amounts
Of fun I knew it was gonna be fun but I just didn't expect it to be that good like
The americanism that was flying around the high fives the yahoos the usa usa the chance it
Was like hilarious and so fun for all the best reasons completely blew my expectations out of the water that
Is going to be it for the video because like technically that part of the California road trip is
Done, but I am 30 minutes off the next leg, which is going to be the next video after
This one.
It is Yosemite National Park.
I have like just set up camp and I'm just pulling into the park now.
Um, it is, I'm going to give you a sneak peek.
We've got no idea what's coming.
Well, I was going to say, you've got no idea what's coming but I also have no idea what's coming
Because I haven't even gone in there yet anyway thank you so much for watching I'm gonna go and catch
Sunset I'll see you guys in the next video for Yosemite bye